Edward R. Murrow Papers MS025
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Books, 1890 -- 1974; MS025.007; 0.55 Linear Feet
  - Rosa Luxemburg; her life and work., 1940; MS025.007.MR.00540; Frlich, Paul, 1884-1953. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Marshall, citizen soldier., 1947; MS025.007.MR.00541; Frye, William R. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription on front flyleaf from author: Dear Mother Atkinson and [?], It would be punishment to ask you to read it again, sine you worried through each stage of it; but I hope you won't find it punishment to have it lying around. With love, Bill. Mr. and Mrs. George Atkinson from William Frye, Prattville, Ala., 2 April 1947. Date is approximate
  - Antarctic adventure: the Commonwealth Trans-Antarctic Expedition, 1955-58., 1959; MS025.007.MR.00542; Fuchs, Vivian, Sir. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Christmas card from Evelyn Wellington inserted on first page after front cover.
  - The decisive battles of the United States., 1942; MS025.007.MR.00543; Fuller, J. F. C. (John Frederick Charles), 1878-1966. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The night of time., 1955; MS025.007.MR.00544; Flp-Miller, Ren, 1891-1963. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription on front flyleaf from author: To Ed Murrow, as a token of gratitude for so many enlightening broadcasts and telecasts throughout the years - Rene Fulop-Miller, 1955. Date is approximate
  - The breakfast war., 1958; MS025.007.MR.00545; Furneaux, Rupert. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Publisher's note inserted on first page after front cover. Date is approximate
  - The final ball; [a novel]., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00546; Gaiser, Gerd, 1908-1976. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The challenge of coexistence., 1957; MS025.007.MR.00547; Gaitskell, Hugh, 1906-1963. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    The Godkin lectures at Harvard University, 1957.
  - Retreat in the East., 1942; MS025.007.MR.00548; Gallagher, O'Dowd. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - After these many quests. [Autobiography]., 1949; MS025.007.MR.00549; Gander, Leonard Marsland, 1902-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf from author: Very best wishes for 1950 to my good friend and ex-warco Ed Murrow. Marsland Gander. Jan., 1950.
  - The birth of Israel; the drama as I saw it., 1948; MS025.007.MR.00550; Garca Granados, Jorge, 1900-1961. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Bookmark from publisher inserted on first page after front cover.
  - Catholic viewpoint on censorship., 1958; MS025.007.MR.00551; Gardiner, Harold C. (Harold Charles), 1904-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Excellence, can we be equal and excellent too?, 1961; MS025.007.MR.00552; Gardner, John William, 1912-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Sterling-dollar diplomacy: Anglo-American collaboration in the reconstruction of multilateral trade., 1956; MS025.007.MR.00553; Gardner, Richard N. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Publisher's card inserted between p.238-39.
  - Be on TV., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00554; Gardner, Richard, 1931-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Letter from author and publisher's note inserted on first page after front cover. Date is approximate
  - Gibraltar and the Mediterranean., 1939; MS025.007.MR.00555; Garratt, G. T. (Geoffrey Theodore), 1888-1942. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The company of men, a novel., 1950; MS025.007.MR.00556; Gary, Romain. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf from author: For Ed Murrow. The American who makes the world a better place. Romain Gray.
  - The call to honour, 1940-1942., 1955; MS025.007.MR.00557; Gaulle, Charles de, 1890-1970. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    War memoirs / Charles de Gaulle, v. 1. Contents: [v. 1] Narrative.
  - War and peace in the space age., 1958; MS025.007.MR.00558; Gavin, James M. (James Maurice), 1907-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Publisher's note inserted at preliminary title page. Date is approximate
  - Japan diary., 1948; MS025.007.MR.00559; Gayn, Mark J., 1909-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Journey from the East., 1944; MS025.007.MR.00560; Gayn, Mark J., 1909-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Franklin Delano Roosevelt, a memorial., 1945; MS025.007.MR.00561; Geddes, Donald Porter, b. 1899. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Annotated. Corners of p.197, 206, 210-11, 226.
  - Fallen bastions; the Central European tragedy., 1939; MS025.007.MR.00562; Gedye, George Eric Rowe, 1890-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Security, loyalty, and science., 1950; MS025.007.MR.00563; Gellhorn, Walter, 1906-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Daily mail war atlas with 32 pages of fully coloured maps covering the belligerent countries, neutral states and principal theaters of war. Complete with large-scale, folding Air view map of the western front., 1940; MS025.007.MR.00564; George Philip & Son. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - God's underground., 1949; MS025.007.MR.00565; George, Father, pseud. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - England in transition; life and work in the eighteenth century., 1931; MS025.007.MR.00566; George, M. Dorothy (Mary Dorothy). (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf: Janet Murrow.
  - Documents on German foreign policy, 1918-1945, from the archives of the German Foreign Ministry., 1949; MS025.007.MR.00567; Germany. Auswrtiges Amt. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Series D (1937-1945), v. 2, Germany and Czechoslovakia, 1937-1938.
  - Documents on German foreign policy, 1918-1945, from the archives of the German Foreign Ministry., 1954; MS025.007.MR.00568; Germany. Auswrtiges Amt. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Series D (1937-1945), v. 9, The War Years, September 4, 1939-March 18, 1940.
  - Documents on German foreign policy, 1918-1945, from the archives of the German Foreign Ministry., 1956; MS025.007.MR.00569; Germany. Auswrtiges Amt. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Series D (1937-1945), v. 9, The War Years, March 18-June 22, 1940.
  - Big government; the meaning and purpose of the Hoover Commission Report., 1949; MS025.007.MR.00570; Gervasi, Frank, 1908-1990. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson and the world., 1966; MS025.007.MR.00571; Geyelin, Philip L. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Books that matter. Date is approximate
  - All men have loved thee, a song of France., 1941; MS025.007.MR.00572; Geyer, Harold C. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Soviet Russia; an introduction., 1946; MS025.007.MR.00573; Gibberd, Kathleen, 1897-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Hugh Gibson, 1883-1954: extracts from his letter and anecdotes from his friends., 1956; MS025.007.MR.00574; Gibson, Hugh, 1883-1954. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Copy #612 of 1000. Editor's business card (Perrin C. Galpin) paper clipped to first page after front cover. Strip of paper with copy #612 (edition limited to 1000 copies) inserted after title page.
  - Years of the locust., 1947; MS025.007.MR.00575; Gielgud, Val Henry, 1900-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Author's signature on title page: Val Gielgud, 1947.
  - Belgium in bondage., 1943; MS025.007.MR.00576; Gijsen, Marnix, 1899-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The man who lives in paradise; the autobiography of A.C. Gilbert., 1954; MS025.007.MR.00577; Gilbert, A. C. (Alfred Carlton), 1884-1961. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The welfare state and the national welfare: a symposium on some of the threatening tendencies of our times., 1952; MS025.007.MR.00578; Glueck, Sheldon, 1896-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Publisher's note inserted on first page after front cover. Stamped: Book Review Copy on inside cover.
  - War criminals: their prosecution & punishment., 1944; MS025.007.MR.00579; Glueck, Sheldon, 1896-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - War criminals: their prosecution & punishment., 1944; MS025.007.MR.00580; Glueck, Sheldon, 1896-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Corner of p.17 is turned down.
  - Forgotten pioneer., 1963; MS025.007.MR.00581; Golden, Harry, 1902-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Publisher's note inserted on first page after front cover. Date is approximate
  - Two-way street, the emergence of the public relations counsel., 1948; MS025.007.MR.00582; Goldman, Eric Frederick, 1915-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The devil's repertoire; or, Nuclear bombing and the life of man., 1959; MS025.007.MR.00583; Gollancz, Victor, 1893-1967. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Publisher's notes inserted on first page after front cover.
  - Rice roots., 1958; MS025.007.MR.00584; Goodfriend, Arthur. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The twisted image., 1963; MS025.007.MR.00585; Goodfriend, Arthur. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - All honorable men; corruption and compromise in American life., 1963; MS025.007.MR.00586; Goodman, Walter. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Atlantic Monthly Press Book. Date is approximate
  - News is a weapon., 1942; MS025.007.MR.00587; Gordon, Matthew, 1910-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Better than communism., 1958; MS025.007.MR.00588; Gordon, Melvin. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - People in colonies., 1948; MS025.007.MR.00589; Goshal, Kumar. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - A geography of Europe., 1950; MS025.007.MR.00590; Gottmann, Jean. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf: Murrow. Date is approximate
  - Year one: an account of the first year of operation of an independent television company in England., 1958; MS025.007.MR.00591; Granada TV Network, Ltd. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Bookmark inserted at front flyleaf.
  - In quest of knowledge; a historical perspective on adult education., 1955; MS025.007.MR.00592; Grattan, C. Hartley (Clinton Hartley), 1902-1980. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Awakened China; the country Americans don't know., 1961; MS025.007.MR.00593; Greene, Felix. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The uncommon man; the individual in the organization., 1959; MS025.007.MR.00594; Greenewalt, Crawford H., 1902-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    McKinsey Foundation lecture series, 1958.
  - American folksongs of protest., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00595; Greenway, John. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Perpetua ed.
  - Your city tomorrow., 1947; MS025.007.MR.00596; Greer, Guy. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Lady Gregory's journals, 1916-1930., 1947; MS025.007.MR.00597; Gregory, Lady, 1852-1932. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Unconditional hatred; German war guilt and the future of Europe., 1953; MS025.007.MR.00598; Grenfell, Russell. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st world ed. Inscription on front flyleaf: Murrow.
  - Years in ambush., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00599; Grenier, Roger, 1919-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Anatomy of a motion picture., 1959; MS025.007.MR.00600; Griffith, Richard, 1912-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Card With the Compliments of Otto Preminger inserted on first page after front cover. Date is approximate
  - The waist-high culture., 1959; MS025.007.MR.00601; Griffith, Thomas (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The British commonwealth: its place in the service of the world., 1943; MS025.007.MR.00602; Grigg, Edward William Macleay, Sir, 1879-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The British commonwealth: its place in the service of the world., 1943; MS025.007.MR.00603; Grigg, Edward William Macleay, Sir, 1879-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Men under stress., 1945; MS025.007.MR.00604; Grinker, Roy R. (Roy Richard), 1900-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The Far Eastern policy of the United States., 1964; MS025.007.MR.00605; Griswold, Alfred Whitney, 1906-1963. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Annotated. Inscription on front flyleaf: Casey Murrow, February 3, 1967.
  - The 5th amendment today; three speeches., 1955; MS025.007.MR.00606; Griswold, Erwin N. (Erwin Nathaniel), 1904-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf: 2/13/56, Ed Murrow, I hope you find this book as persuasive as I did and hope you use your great influence in putting the 5th Amendment back into the Constitution, after the no nothings almost knocked it out. Victor Sharrow.
  - The United Nations: structure for peace., 1962; MS025.007.MR.00607; Gross, Ernest A. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Polish western territories., 1959; MS025.007.MR.00608; Gruchaman, Bohdan. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Errata slip inserted on last page.
  - An eye in the sky., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00609; Grudin, Louis, 1898-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Limited 1st ed. Date is approximate
  - Power and responsibility: a course of action for the new age., 1961; MS025.007.MR.00610; Guardini, Romano, 1885-1968. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The hundred years., 1937; MS025.007.MR.00611; Guedalla, Philip, 1889-1944. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Roosevelt's good neighbor policy., 1950; MS025.007.MR.00612; Guerrant, Edward O., 1911-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    This is a publication of The School of Inter-American Affairs, The University of New Mexico, Inter-American Studies V. Publisher's note inserted on first page after front cover.
  - The Guinness book of records., 1956; MS025.007.MR.00613; Guiness Superlatives Limited (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf: To Casey, with love from Hilary. London, 1956. Date is approximate
  - Inside Asia., 1939; MS025.007.MR.00614; Gunther, John, 1901-1970. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Inside U.S.A., 1947; MS025.007.MR.00615; Gunther, John, 1901-1970. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription on preliminary title page: Best wishes to Ed Murrow. John Gunther. NY City. May 7, 1947.
  - Inside U.S.A., 1947; MS025.007.MR.00616; Gunther, John, 1901-1970. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on preliminary title page: For Edward R. Murrow (once more!). John Gunther. February 1948. (Through the courtesy of our mutual friend Saul Haas).
  - Roosevelt in Retrospect, a profile in history., 1950; MS025.007.MR.00617; Gunther, John, 1901-1970. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Cape to cape by wheelchair; covering almost fifty thousand travel miles, proving that for everyone the world extends far beyond the horizon, and not just to the four walls., 1959; MS025.007.MR.00618; Gutman, Ernest M. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf: 1/30/61 To Ed Murrow, a great newsman, with my best regards. Ernest M. Gutman.
  - The Nation's safety and arms control., 1961; MS025.007.MR.00619; Hadley, Arthur Twining, 1924-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Publisher's card inserted at front flyleaf
  - Operation Deep Freeze '61: Task Force 43., 1961; MS025.007.MR.00620; Hahn, James S. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Cover title.
  - American strategy for the nuclear age., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00621; Hahn, Walter F. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - American strategy for the nuclear age., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00622; Hahn, Walter F. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - American strategy for the nuclear age., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00623; Hahn, Walter F. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - In the shadow of Russia; Eastern Europe in the postwar world., 1959; MS025.007.MR.00624; Halasz, Nicholas, 1895-1985. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - A.R.P., 1938; MS025.007.MR.00625; Haldane, J. B. S. (John Burdon Sanderson), 1892-1964. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Left Book Club ed. Left Book Club pamphlets inserted between p.156-57 and last page of book.
  - The march of freedom; a layman's history of the American people., 1947; MS025.007.MR.00626; Hale, William Harlan, 1910-1974. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription of front flyleaf: To Ed Murrow who has thought about these things. Greetings, Bill Hale.
  - Rocketry and space exploration., 1958; MS025.007.MR.00627; Haley, Andrew Gallagher. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The folks at home., 1952; MS025.007.MR.00628; Halsey, Margaret, 1910-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf: Murrow.
  - Three against Lincoln: Murat Halstead reports the caucuses of 1860., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00629; Halstead, Murat, 1829-1908. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - A peak in Darien: a novel., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00630; Ham, Roswell G. (Roswell Gray), d. 1947. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf from author: For Edward R. Murrow, with regard - Roswell G. Ham, Jr. August 1960. Date is approximate
  - Look into happiness., 1962; MS025.007.MR.00631; Ham, Roswell G. (Roswell Gray), d. 1947. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Majority, 1931-1952: an anthology of 21 years of publishing., MS025.007.MR.00632; Hamish Hamilton Ltd. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf from Jamie Hamilton, founder of Hamish Hamilton: To my friend, Ed Murrow, who does as fine work in peace as he did in war, with admiration and warm regards from Jamie Hamilton, February 1953. Date is approximate
  - The struggle for Indochina., 1954; MS025.007.MR.00633; Hammer, Ellen J. (Ellen Joy), 1921-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Published under the auspices of the Institute of Pacific Relations. Advance Review Copy sticker affixed to front cover.
  - After Nehru, who?, 1963; MS025.007.MR.00634; Hangen, Welles, 1930-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Publisher's note inserted at front flyleaf. Date is approximate
  - Picket and the pen; the Pat Gorman story., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00635; Hanna, Hilton E. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on inside cover from author: To Edward R. Murrow - Director U.S. Information Service - with admiration and respect for your contributions, through the years, to the stimulation as well as awakening of social conscience and every good wish that your labors in behalf of your fellow men will continue ever fervent in the days ahead! Sincerely, Hilton Hanna, 3/8/61. See p. 380. Hilton Hanna's business card inserted at front flyleaf. Date is approximate
  - Ten lean years: an examination of the record of the national government in the field of unemployment., 1940; MS025.007.MR.00636; Hannington, Wal, 1895-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The problems of the distressed areas., 1937; MS025.007.MR.00637; Hannington, Wal, 1895-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Left Book Club ed. Inscription on front flyleaf: J.H.B. Murrow, November, 1937-. Left book club flier inserted at Table of Contents page. Left Book Club pamphlets inserted between p.78-9, 100-101, 196-97
  - The world almanac and book of facts for 1954., MS025.007.MR.00638; Hansen, Harry, 1884-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Sixty-ninth year of publication. Date is approximate
  - The world almanac and book of facts, 1963., MS025.007.MR.00639; Hansen, Harry, 1884-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Seventy-eighth year of issue. Date is approximate
  - Transformation: the story of modern Puerto Rico., 1955; MS025.007.MR.00640; Hanson, Earl Parker, b. 1899. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Communist America--must it be?, 1960; MS025.007.MR.00641; Hargis, Billy James, 1925-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The Russia I believe in; the memoirs of Samuel N. Harper, 1902-1941., 1945; MS025.007.MR.00642; Harper, Samuel N. (Samuel Northrup), 1882-1943. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Signed by the author on the title page.
  - Seven years in Tibet., 1954; MS025.007.MR.00643; Harrer, Heinrich, 1912-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Publisher's note inserted between p.96-7.
  - It's your business., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00644; Harriman, John, 1904-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - It's your business., 1960; MS025.007.MR.00645; Harriman, John, 1904-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Peace with Russia?, 1959; MS025.007.MR.00646; Harriman, W. Averell (William Averell), 1891-1986. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Flyer for new book by author The Test Ban Treaty inserted at front flyleaf.
  - The other America: poverty in the United States., 1962; MS025.007.MR.00647; Harrington, Michael, 1928-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Oscar Wilde: his life & confessions., 1930; MS025.007.MR.00648; Harris, Frank, 1855-1931. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Iraq: its people, its society, its culture, 1958; MS025.007.MR.00649; Harris, George Lawrence, 1910-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Is there a Republican majority?: political trends, 1952-1956., 1954; MS025.007.MR.00650; Harris, Louis, 1921-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription on front flyleaf from author: For Ed Murrow - Elmo Roper tells me you have an allergy to polls, but in his opinion, it won't hurt you much to read this. Louis Harris. Date is approximate
  - The real voice., 1964; MS025.007.MR.00651; Harris, Richard, 1926-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)